

Salman Alfarissy

IT Programmer | Software Engineer | Web Developer

+62 822 8503 2741

salman.alfarissy26@gmail.com

Sumatera Barat, Indonesia

Skills

- · Programming Languages: PHP, JavaScript, Java, Kotlin.
- · Web Technologies & Frameworks: HTML, CSS, jQuery, Vue.js, Livewire, Laravel, Yii, NestJS.
- Mobile Development: Flutter, Android.
- · Software Architecture & Design Patterns: MVC, Repository Pattern.
- Tools & Version Control: Git, Figma.
- Development Methodologies :
- Design & User Experience: UX Design.

Hobbies & Interest

- Movie
- Book
- Traveling

Links and Credentials





<u>Github</u>



Website



<u>Instagram</u>

About

I have experiences as a web developer for the last 2 years. Technology stacks that have been used are PHP, JavaScript, jQuery, CSS, Livewire, and Laravel. Each project development has been implementing a clean architecture using repository pattern.

I can do collaborative work and always curious of new things. To maintain projects with the team, we use version control (Github/Gitlab). Furthermore, when the world changing, I always discovering and learning the latest technology. Besides, I also played around with Flutter, Android, and frontend stuff like Vue.js.

I believe that my experience and skills will contribute to the successful development and creation of web or mobile applications.

Education

2018 - 2022

 Politeknik Negeri Padang **Bachelor of Applied Software Engineering**

GPA: 3.68/4.00

Experience



Islamic Boarding School Mumtaza Prapas Banjarnegara (mumtaza.id)

IT Programmer | Oct 2024 - Present

As an independent IT Programmer at Islamic Boarding School Mumtaza Prapas Banjarnegara, I was fully responsible for developing a web-based information system from scratch. My work involved analyzing user requirements, designing system architecture, and building both backend and frontend using Laravel, Livewire, ¡Query, and Bootstrap. I also created responsive and user-friendly UI designs with Figma, managed the MySQL database through DBeaver, and handled deployment and maintenance via cPanel and Webnesia. The system was designed to support administrative and academic operations, including new student registration, student and guardian data management, payment tracking, and activity fundraising. This project required a mix of technical expertise and selfmanagement to ensure successful end-to-end development and system reliability.



Celeb Star Sdn Bhd (celebshare.co)

Software Engineer | Jan 2023 - Mar 2024

As a Software Engineer at Celeb Star Sdn. Bhd., my role involves contributing to the web development process and ensuring the smooth functioning of all web features. I utilize skills such as Laravel, Livewire, MySQL, JavaScript, jQuery, and Ajax in my development tasks.



PT Garuda Cyber Indonesia

Web Developer | Jul 2021 - Jan 2022

During my internship as a web developer, my responsibilities encompassed the web creation process. I utilized the Laravel framework for website development, and MySQL for database management.